Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society Genealogical Vertical Files ARC.313
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn Historical Society Genealogical Vertical Files
1899-1996
Brooklyn Historical Society
ARC.313
5 linear feet in 6 record cartons
This collection was compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff to organize their genealogical research and the research of other professional and amateur genealogists. The collection includes correspondence, newspaper clippings, notes, pedigree charts, and a limited number of photographs.
Biographical / Historical
This collection was compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff to organize their genealogical research and the research of other professional and amateur genealogists.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes compiled genealogical research, including correspondence, newspaper clippings, notes, pedigree charts, and a limited number of photographs. The files represent families from Long Island and the North East region of the United States, and also reflect on the institutional history of the Brooklyn Historical Society. Materials in the collections are both originals and reproductions.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research without restrictions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by family name.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This is an artificial collection, compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff at an unknown date.
Kings County (N.Y.) |x Genealogy; Long Island (N.Y.) |x Genealogy; Brooklyn Historical Society
- Abrams, undated (Box 1)
- Adams, Addoms, undated (Box 1)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Compiled or donated by Lewis P Addoms
- Ager, undated (Box 1)
- Andrews, Hooper, 1953 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Helen Martha Wright, Mary F. Brogan
- Angel, Curran, Corwin, Curwin, Sweet, Wiltsie, Willsey, 1963 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Miss Virginia Ford, Gertrude A. Barber
- Austin, 1944 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Raymond Austin Wheeler, Mrs. Moore
- Austin, Austen, 1973 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by John H. Lindenbusch, Executive Director, Mr. Theodore P. Sherris
- Aylett, undated (Box 1)
- Babbott, Pratt, 1974 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Stryker-Rhodda, Elizabeth French Babbott
- Bailey, Barnes, 1905 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Frederic W Bailey, Mrs. H.B. Barnes
- Bailey, undated (Box 1)
- Balfe, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by William M. Miller
- Barber, 1960 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Gertrude A. Barber
- Barkeloo, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Teunis G. Bergen
- Barker, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Edna Huntington
- Barnes, undated (Box 1)
- Barnes, Joseph Philip, undated (Box 1)
- Barto, undated (Box 1)
- Bayles, 1944 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Helen M. Wright and others
- Beebe, undated (Box 1)
- Beebe, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Paul W. Prindle
- Bellinger, 1934 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by L.F. Bellinger
- Benson, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Marilyn Souders
- Benson, 1939 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Arthur D. Benson
- Berry, 1975 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Louis Duermyer, Mrs. Thomas H. Giddings (Jane Fuller Berry)
- Billings, undated (Box 1)
- Bleoo, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Theodore W. Roth
- Board, Boord, Bourd, Borde, Boorde, Bord, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Harry Percy Boord, M.A. Cambridge
- Boas, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Walter J Boas
- Boerum, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Franklin Burdge, Tunis G. Bergen
- Boerum II, 1965 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Evelyn S. Wachter
- Booth, 1955 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Gertrude A. Barber, Mrs. Alvire C. (Booth) Rich
- Borden, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Media Research Bureau, Washington D.C., Elizabeth Haviland
- Boyd, undated (Box 1)
- Bradt, 1933 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Annie Scott Baxter
- Brady, undated (Box 1)
- Brown, Halstead, 1960 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. T.S. Hill, Gertrude A Barker
- Brown, Gordon, 1953 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Emile Neumann
- Bragaw, Hathaway, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. D.G. Hathaway
- Bray, undated (Box 1)
- Briand, undated (Box 1)
- Bruen, 1994 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by John Andrew Sass
- Buckingham, Martin, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Emile Neumann (Mrs. Fannie) from the files of D.A.R.
- Burden, undated (Box 1)
- Burhan's Family Bible, undated (Box 1)
- Burrows, Buroughs, Burris, Burriss, Burrous, Burroughs, etc., 1965 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mabel A. Sheppard and Lillian A. Sheppard
- Burt, 1956 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. G. A. Barber
- Burtis, undated (Box 1)
- Cady, 1935 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Enterprise and News
- Campbell, undated (Box 1)
- Carlin, Carman, Miller, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Charles L Carlin
- Carman, 1952 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Walter F. Wright, Walter F. Wright
- Carman, 1966 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Mary Carman Fraby
- Carman-Pettit, 1966 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Marg Gordon C. Elliott
- Casler, 1972 (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Claire M. Wilkinson
- Carpenter, undated (Box 1)
- Carter, undated (Box 1)
- Chamberlain, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Sarah A. Davison
- Chamberlin, Oliver, Smith, undated (Box 1)
- Chapman, undated (Box 1)
- Chase, undated (Box 1)
- Chase, undated (Box 1)
- Churchill, 1899 (Box 1)
- Churchill, Mathews, undated (Box 1)
- Clarke, undated (Box 1)
- Clarkson, undated (Box 1)
  Compiled or donated by Miss Helen Clarkson and Miss Maud Dilliard
- Clearman, undated (Box 1)
- Clearman, Coger, undated (Box 1)
- Clements, Powers, undated (Box 1)
- Cleveland, undated (Box 1)
- Close, undated (Box 1)
- Closson, undated (Box 1)
- Clowes, undated (Box 1)
- Cobb (Blacksmith), 1981 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Duane Phillips Cobb, esq and Capt. Mortimer Howell Cobb
- Cole, Bergen, undated (Box 2)
- Colell, undated (Box 2)
- Congdon, 1954 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Charles T. Middlebrook, Harriet Stryker-Rodda
- Conklin, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by J.P. Conklin
- Connors, Walsh, undated (Box 2)
- Corey, Cory, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Charles Estabrook Cory
- Cornell, Cornwall, Cornwell, undated (Box 2)
- Cornwell, 1996 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Gale Thomas Cornwell
- Cooper, Cock, Dominick, 1924 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by John Anderson Jr
- Cooper, Reeve, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by William A. Robbins
- Couwenhoven, undated (Box 2)
- Crocker, undated (Box 2)
- Cropsey, undated (Box 2)
- Croquet, Polhemus, Jeroleman, undated (Box 2)
- Cundall, Bennett, 1919 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Frank Haviland
- Curran, Corwin, Curwin, undated (Box 2)
- Cuvelier, Cuvilje, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Herbert F. Seversmith, Mr. Evelyn P. Luquer
- Darrow, undated (Box 2)
- Davall, D'Eyville, McLaughlin, Early, Betagh, Bonar, undated (Box 2)
- Davies, 1926 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Daisy Hitch Davies
- Davis, 1935 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Law Voge (??)
- Davis, undated (Box 2)
- Davison, French, Richardson, Prescott, Chamberlain, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Sarah A. Davison Sarah M. Davison
- Davison, undated (Box 2)
- De Groat, Edward, 1971 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Walter Bradford De Groat
- De Groat, undated (Box 2)
- De La Vergne, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Anna C. Gilman, Evelyn Briggs Baldwin
- Denison, Thompson, 1961 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Mr. John Dorrance Morrell, Mr. John Dorrance Morrell
- Devan, undated (Box 2)
- Devaney, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Bernard A. Kearns
- Devendorf, undated (Box 2)
- Dewitt, Tjerck, Classen, undated (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Vona E. DeWitt Smith, Dr. Carolyn Smith Pellettier
- Dietrich, Pleffner, Roos, Metz, 1982 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Robert R. Davenport
- Dockstader, 1934 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by J.M. Dockstader
- Doremus, Townsend, Gardner, Deas, undated (Box 2)
- Driver, undated (Box 2)
- Druse, undated (Box 2)
- Dunkelberger, 1966 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Frederick J. Simmons
- Durkee, undated (Box 2)
- Duryea, 1949 (Box 2)
  Compiled or donated by Miss Anna E. Dyrea
- Mol, Banta, Hartje, undated (Box 2)
- Faile, undated (Box 3)
- Fetcher, Voege, undated (Box 3)
- Fengado, undated (Box 3)
- Ferris, 1935 (Box 3)
- Ferris, Ferriers, undated (Box 3)
- Ferris, Storm, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Morris P. Ferris
- Fountain, 1984 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by William A. Eardeley, annotated by A.S.W. Wardwell
- Freeman, Crowell, 1963 (Box 3)
- Frisbie, undated (Box 3)
- Fryer, undated (Box 3)
- Gallaudet, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Anna Gallaudet Beeny
- Gatchell, 1964 (Box 3)
- Gautier, undated (Box 3)
- Giddings, Georgia R., undated (Box 3)
- Gignoux, undated (Box 3)
- Glover, Nichols, Kimball, undated (Box 3)
- Goennert, undated (Box 3)
- Golding, undated (Box 3)
- Goss, Van der Goss, undated (Box 3)
- Green, Thorne, Parsons, Bowne, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Charles E. Tuttle Company
- Greenfield, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. C.H. Austin
- Griffeth, undated (Box 3)
- Griffin, Griffen, 1995 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Paul J. Griffin
- Hadley, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Miss Helen M. Wright
- Haggerty, undated (Box 3)
- Hallowell, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Robert Corwin Hallowell
- Hamilton, Pritchard, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Walter S. Anderson
- Hamlin, Kimball, Tyler, undated (Box 3)
- Harned, undated (Box 3)
- Harris, undated (Box 3)
- Harrison, undated (Box 3)
- Hart, undated (Box 3)
- Hasbrouck, undated (Box 3)
- Hees, Hase, Hayes, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Leslie A. Frye
- Hegeman, 1994 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Jeannette Marie Ruddy Krauszer (Mrs. Nicholas R.)
- Hempstead, 1950 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Herman A. Noyes, Mrs. M.W. Benn
- Henlin, undated (Box 3)
- Herkimer, 1933 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by L.F. Bellinger and Albert Livingston Marshall
- Hernandez, 1987 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Randolph James Hernandez, Michael William Hernandez
- Hewitt, undated (Box 3)
- Hibbs, Carter, Blaker, Buckman, Lyons, Burrows, Sheppard, undated (Box 3)
- Higbe, undated (Box 3)
- Hillman, undated (Box 3)
- Hix, Hicks, undated (Box 3)
- Hoffman, undated (Box 3)
- Holmes, 1954 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Agnes Bouton Holmes
- Hopper, Hoppe, Hooper, Tone, undated (Box 3)
- Horton, undated (Box 3)
- Hotchkiss, 1961 (Box 3)
- House, 1933 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by M.R. Shaver
- Howland, undated (Box 3)
- Hoyt, undated (Box 3)
- Huguenot Surnames, undated (Box 3)
- Hunt, 1949 (Box 3)
- Huntley, 1960 (Box 3)
- Hyde, undated (Box 3)
- Ingersol, Tuthill, 1962 (Box 3)
- Ivers, Gallagher, 1968 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Helen Ball, Helen Ball
- Jacques, Jaquith, 1949 (Box 3)
- Jameson, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Helena Tarkington
- Jayne, 1993 (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Milton W. Bush Jr.
- Jaynes, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by John L. Vinke
- Jefferson, Jepperson, Jepherson, undated (Box 3)
- Jencks, Mowry, undated (Box 3)
- Jenkins, undated (Box 3)
- Jermain, Jordan, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Madeleine Winslow
- Johnson, undated (Box 3)
- Johnson, undated (Box 3)
  Compiled or donated by Janet Johnson
- Johnston, undated (Box 3)
- Jordan, undated (Box 3)
- Kehr, undated (Box 4)
- Kelley, Kelly, undated (Box 4)
- Kernochan, Carnoughan, undated (Box 4)
- Kincaid, Kinkaid, Kinkead, Kinkade, undated (Box 4)
- Kingsland, undated (Box 4)
- Koehler, undated (Box 4)
- Kouwenhoven, 1977 (Box 4)
- Kowenhoven, Bennett, undated (Box 4)
- Landfear, undated (Box 4)
- Lawrence, undated (Box 4)
- Layton, undated (Box 4)
- Lefferts, undated (Box 4)
- Leland, undated (Box 4)
- Lepper, 1933 (Box 4)
- Liningtons, undated (Box 4)
- Litchfield, undated (Box 4)
- Longyear, undated (Box 4)
- Lott, undated (Box 4)
- Lott, undated (Box 4)
- Lott, undated (Box 4)
- Low, Lee, Carter, Martin, Brown, North, Hoyt, Whipple, undated (Box 4)
- Lowe, undated (Box 4)
- Ludlow, undated (Box 4)
- Ludlow, Hanmer, 1963 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Russell Cruikshank, Mrs. Constance Gustafson
- Luyster, undated (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Halstead H. Frost Jr.
- Mac Crate, McCrate, 1967 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Frederick K. Gross
- Mansfield, Arnold, Lovell, Bay, 1938 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Ellen Harrell Cantrell
- Mapes, undated (Box 4)
- Mapes, undated (Box 4)
- Markham, undated (Box 4)
- Marshall, 1934 (Box 4)
- Mason, undated (Box 4)
- Maxim, 1966 (Box 4)
- Mayhew, undated (Box 4)
- Mc Cowan, McCowan, Benwell, undated (Box 4)
- McDougall, Harsha, Flack, undated (Box 4)
- McDougall, undated (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Maj. John E. Coderre and Anita Coderre
- McDougall, 1963 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Esther W. Osborne, John D. Morrell
- McIver, MacIver, Mac Iver, Mc Iver, undated (Box 4)
- Messerve, 1960 (Box 4)
- Miller, undated (Box 4)
- Miller, 1958 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Margaret V. Wall
- Miller, undated (Box 4)
- Miner, Clapp, 1961 (Box 4)
- Moody, undated (Box 4)
- Moore, undated (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Charles B. Moore
- Moore, Brigham, undated (Box 4)
- Moore, North, 1979 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Thoedore D. Rushmore
- Morton, 1931 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Daniel Morton
- Mosher, 1934 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by William C. Mosher
- Mosher, Wilson, undated (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Mr. Vincent F. Seyfried
- Mott, undated (Box 4)
- Moyer, Bell, undated (Box 4)
- Mulford, 1929 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Teunis D. Huntting
- Mundy, undated (Box 4)
- Murphy, 1935 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Paul B. Mattice
- Murphy, 1973 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Michael E. Chase, Michael E. Chase
- Neal, Dockendorff, undated (Box 4)
- Nelson-Hodges, undated (Box 4)
- Newman, undated (Box 4)
- Nichols, Cox, undated (Box 4)
- Norcross, undated (Box 4)
- Nostrand, undated (Box 4)
- Onderdonk, undated (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Henry Onderdonk Jr.
- Osborn, undated (Box 4)
- Palmer, 1939 (Box 4)
- Paine, van Bergen, Webb, Matson, undated (Box 4)
- Parker, undated (Box 4)
- Pearce, Pierce, 1982 (Box 4)
- Pell, Thompson, undated (Box 4)
- Peppe, undated (Box 4)
- Peter, undated (Box 4)
- Pettit, undated (Box 4)
- Philbrick, undated (Box 4)
- Place, undated (Box 4)
- Pomeroy, 1966 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by John D. Fish, B. Ann Moorhouse
- Prescott, undated (Box 4)
- Priest, 1979 (Box 4)
  Compiled or donated by Eunice Knight Russell Priest and Eunice Russell Bastedo Scribner
- Prince, undated (Box 4)
- Rapalje, undated (Box 5)
- Rath, Kolkebeck, undated (Box 5)
- Rayner, undated (Box 5)
- Redfield, Platt, undated (Box 5)
- Redman, undated (Box 5)
- Reed, Fitch, undated (Box 5)
- Remsen, undated (Box 5)
- Reynold, undated (Box 5)
- Rich, Robinson, Tyler, York, undated (Box 5)
- Richardson, Fletcher, Fledger, Pierce, Pearce, Peirce, undated (Box 5)
- Richmond, 1963 (Box 5)
- Rider, undated (Box 5)
- Ridgway, undated (Box 5)
- Robbins, Jordan, Treadwell, Stevens, undated (Box 5)
- Robinson, Sherman, Farrar, Hayward, Winship, undated (Box 5)
- Rockefeller, undated (Box 5)
- Rogers, undated (Box 5)
- Roosevelt, undated (Box 5)
- Rosencrans, William J. Coulter, undated (Box 5)
- Rosenkrans, William J. Coulter, 1966 (Box 5)
- Ross, Carter, Abercrombie, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Dorothy Julia Ross
- Rowley, undated (Box 5)
- Runyon, undated (Box 5)
- Russell, undated (Box 5)
- Ryder, undated (Box 5)
- Saltsman, 1933 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Marilyn L. Fox Watkins
- Sands, undated (Box 5)
- Sanford, Swannell, McMinn, Lane, Ivins, undated (Box 5)
- Sasser, undated (Box 5)
- Sawyer, undated (Box 5)
- Schenck, undated (Box 5)
- Schramling, 1967 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by George E. Schramling
- Scidmore, Skidmore, 1973 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Kay Perry (Mrs. George B.)
- Scudder, undated (Box 5)
- Searing, undated (Box 5)
- Shaner, undated (Box 5)
- Shepard, Shepherd, Sheppard, undated (Box 5)
- Sizer, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Henry G. Holch
- Skinner, undated (Box 5)
- Slack, Slaght, Slight, undated (Box 5)
- Smith, Treen, undated (Box 5)
- Smith, Rock Smith, Howard Smith, Ireland, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Arthur Soper Wardell
- Snell, 1933 (Box 5)
- Snow, Hallet, undated (Box 5)
- Spear, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by George McKenzie Roberts
- Spencer, 1962 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Theresa Snow Hill, Gertrude A. Barber
- Sprague, Van Buskirk, Wood, undated (Box 5)
- Sprague, undated (Box 5)
- Sroczyk, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Theodore Roth
- Staats, States, Reuben Brown, Burdick, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Elizabeth States Stonington
- Stansbury, undated (Box 5)
- Stevens, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Edwin A. Stevens, Sr., William A. Robbins
- Stevens, undated (Box 5)
- Stilwell, Stillwell, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Hetty Stillwell Lee
- Stoothoff, undated (Box 5)
- Stuyvesant, Peter Gerard, undated (Box 5)
- Suffern, Sloat, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Lewis P. Addoms
- Sullivan, undated (Box 5)
- Suydam, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Edward Suydam
- Swain, Tooker, undated (Box 5)
- Sweet, undated (Box 5)
- Tappen, Tappan, Topping, undated (Box 5)
- Thomas, Truman, undated (Box 5)
- Tillotson, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by William Leslie Tillotson
- Titus, undated (Box 5)
- Tkach, undated (Box 5)
- Toedteberg, undated (Box 5)
- Topping, 1935 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Ada D. De Laney
- Totten, undated (Box 5)
- Tower, undated (Box 5)
- Trivisonno, Traversone, undated (Box 5)
- Tuggle, Post, undated (Box 5)
- Tuthill, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Cyrus B. Tuthill
- Vale, undated (Box 5)
- Valentine, 1935 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Phebe J. Valentine
- Valentine, undated (Box 5)
- Valentine, undated (Box 5)
- Van Alen, undated (Box 5)
- Van Alstine, Schrembling, Ehle, Failing, undated (Box 5)
- Van Brocklin, undated (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Walter L. Van Brocklin
- Van Brunt, 1960 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Nelson N. Van Brunt
- Van Brunt, undated (Box 5)
- Van Brunt, undated (Box 5)
- Van Cleef, undated (Box 5)
- Van Den Bergh, Van Der Poel, Van Everen, Van Alstyne, Van Schaick, 1961 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Catherine Witherhead Taggart, John D. Morrell
- Vanderbeek, undated (Box 5)
- Vanderveer, undated (Box 5)
- Van Derveer, undated (Box 5)
- Van Dyck, undated (Box 5)
- Van Giesen, undated (Box 5)
- Van Horn, undated (Box 5)
- Van Horne, undated (Box 5)
- Van Houten, undated (Box 5)
- Vanleer, 1936 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by M. Stanley Black, Mrs. Emile Neumann
- Van Sinderen, undated (Box 5)
- Van Sise, Van Sysen, 1978 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Gerald Van Sise Raynor
- Van Winkle, Rohr, undated (Box 5)
- Van Wyck, 1924 (Box 5)
  Compiled or donated by Morris P. Ferris, Mrs. Morris P, Ferris
- Veeder, undated (Box 6)
- Velsor, undated (Box 6)
- Verity, undated (Box 6)
- Viele, undated (Box 6)
- Virgin, undated (Box 6)
- Von Der Heid, undated (Box 6)
- Voorhees, undated (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Wheeler N. Vorhees
- Voorhees, Stowitts, undated (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by F.J.V. Stowitts
- Vrooman, undated (Box 6)
- Wadlin, undated (Box 6)
- Wallace, Runnells, Wood, Gledhill, undated (Box 6)
- Walrath, Woldrod, Walradt, 1934 (Box 6)
- Wansor, undated (Box 6)
- Waring, undated (Box 6)
- Warner, undated (Box 6)
- Warner, Britton, undated (Box 6)
- Warren, Burgess, Roosevelt, undated (Box 6)
- Washington County Families, Beardsley, Covel, Aldrich, Pattyson, Roorbach, Hedden, Fish, Tyler, Carmichael, Zimmerman, Fake, Spencer, Pattison, 1939 (Box 6)
- Watson, Jenkens, undated (Box 6)
- Watt, undated (Box 6)
- Waugh, undated (Box 6)
- Webb, 1979 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Donald D. Webb
- Weeks, undated (Box 6)
- Weiser, undated (Box 6)
- Wemple, undated (Box 6)
- West, 1966 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Joseph Keppler
- West, undated (Box 6)
- White, undated (Box 6)
- White, undated (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Richard C. Pace
- White, Silas, undated (Box 6)
- Whytlaw, undated (Box 6)
- Wiggins, Mullikin, Berrien, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Charles F. Limberg
- Willes, Willis, Wills, Wyllys, undated (Box 6)
- Willits, undated (Box 6)
- Willetts, Franklin, Coles, Hewlett, Hegeman, undated (Box 6)
- Williams, undated (Box 6)
- Williams, undated (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by The Media Research Bureau, Elizabeth Haviland
- Willink, undated (Box 6)
- Willis, undated (Box 6)
- Wiltse, Schenck, Brett, 1924 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Morris P. Ferris
- Wiltsie, Willsey, undated (Box 6)
- Wolenska, undated (Box 6)
- Wood, undated (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Franklin Edwards
- Wood, 1966 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Mrs. Ernest A. Ewers
- Woodbury, 1960 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by William Applebie Eardley
- Woolsey, 1968 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by James LW. Woolsey
- Woolsey, 1974 (Box 6)
- Worth, Jessup, undated (Box 6)
- Wright, undated (Box 6)
- Wyckoff, undated (Box 6)
- Wyman, 1961 (Box 6)
- Yarrington, undated (Box 6)
- Young, undated (Box 6)
- Youngs, 1965 (Box 6)
  Compiled or donated by Herbert F. Seversmith
- Zolver, undated (Box 6)
- Zollver, undated (Box 6)
- Zuslavsky, undated (Box 6)